Get ready to pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua
and catch the fire to cross the bridge into 2014 - the year of glory, the year of destiny,
the year of crossing the bridge
Catch the fire.
Viewers, catch the fire
to cross the bridge.
This is the year of glory, the year of destiny.
I don't know the situation you are facing; Jesus knows.
No matter the difficulty or the situation that you are in over there -
are you on the sick bed?
Whatever name they call that sickness,
nothing can change your destiny!
Viewers what can separate you?
Can that sickness separate you?
Can affliction separate you?
Can Infirmity separate you?
Nothing can separate you.
Viewers at home, I command your dream of many years -
come true!
Dream of breakthrough - come true!
Dream of good health - come true!
Dream of prosperity - come to fulfilment!
Dream of long life - come true!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus’ Name
In Jesus' name.
You have discovered yourself.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus’ Name
CR Robert Begier 17/04/2019